And for those who don't
know, he was diagnosed with
autism when he was about
23 months old, I'm trying
to keep it together. So
for me, the biggest thing
for me was, once I
got the diagnosis, I wanted
him to be as independent
of me as possible. And
baby, my 10-year-old walks up
to him and goes, then
why did you choose to
live with mom at 18?
He was like, cuz she's
preparing me for my life,
she's preparing me for college.
Now this is a boy
who couldn't talk, okay? He
was this kid. And he
said, she allows me to
be more of a man
at her house. And he
said, sorry guys. It's okay.
And for him to have
talked about this school since
he was eight years old.
And for him to wanna
be a zoologist when he
grows up. My god. What
school is it? He didn't
wait for me, he didn't
wait for his dad. He
just did it and people
were saying he wasn't gonna
get into this school. Both
my kids are really nice
people. Yeah. And so for
him to recognize what I'm
trying to do, he was
like, mommy helps us be
independent, Zeke. And then Zeke
turns around to me and
he goes, mom, you're in
my safe place.
What 10-year-old says that to
somebody and- That's amazing. That
speaks to how you- With
a good mother. Yeah, that
speaks to what a good
mother you are. We are
so happy and proud of
what you're doing.